Niko Setiawan Pakunegoro

081383870011 | nikosetiawanp@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/nikosetiawanp | github.com/nikosetiawanp

ABOUT ME

I cherish independence and schedule flexibility as a front-end developer. I want to be a proficient individual contributor in front end development who can support people in finding solutions to their issues. My experience in the design industry, working with design teams, ability to manage various client expectations and projects, and excellent communication skill with stakeholders set me apart from other candidates. I'm also used to working with minimum supervision and tight deadlines.

EDUCATION

RevoU (January, 2023 – August, 2023)

Full-stack Software Engineering

RevoU is an Online Academy that prepares students across Indonesia for most in-demand tech jobs.

Unika Soegijapranata

(August, 2016 – August, 2020)

GPA: 3.16

Bachelor Degree of Architecture (S.Ars)

SKILLS AND CERTIFICATIONS

Technical Skills:

Programming Languages: Javascript, Typescript

Front End Development: Next JS, React JS, Tailwind CSS, SCSS / SASS, HTML5, CSS3, Material UI, Electron

JS

Back End Development: Next JS, Nest.js, Express.js, Node.js, REST API, Docker

Database Management: PostgreSQL, SQLite, MongoDB

Tools:

Platforms: GCP, Supabase, Vercel, Netlify, Github

Wireframing and Prototyping: Figma, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe Photoshop

Certifications:

| 1. Certificate of Achievements, RevoU | (August 5, 2023) |
|--|-------------------|
| 2. The Complete Javascript Course 2023, Udemy | (July 24, 2023) |
| 3. 50 Projects in 50 Days - HTML, CSS, Javascript, Udemy | (August 31, 2023) |
| 4. Node.js, Express, MongoDB & More, Udemy | (August 31, 2023) |

PROJECTS

- **Product Feedback App**: Built with React JS, SASS/SCSS, Typescript, Supabase.
- Kanban Task Management App: Built with Next JS, React JS, Tailwind CSS, Typescript, Supabase
- ChatterBox Group Chat App: Built with React JS, Socket IO, Tailwind CSS, Typescript, Express JS

WORKING EXPERIENCES

Part Time Social Media Designer, Vorch Auto

(August, 2018 - August, 2019)

• Created 20+ visual assets and design for social media with minimum supervision from the owner.

Architect, Vide Architecture Studio

(March, 2021 – July, 2021)

Handled 6 architecture and interior projects simultaneously with tight deadlines.

Architect & Graphic Designer, Freelance

(January, 2022 - June, 2023)

• Handled 4 architecture and interior design projects and 3 brand guide projects with minimum supervision.